http://www.0-21.co.uk/index.php/privacy-policy.html

Your 0-21
[Login/out]
Our Commitment
Your privacy is important to us.
To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.
The Information
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the 0-21 website. Types of personal information collected at these pages are:
Full Name
Postal Address
Email address
Information Use
We use the information you provide about yourself when registering only to complete that registration process. Selective address details are required for posing trip information.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose.
We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
We will never share any information given on this site to and third-parties.
Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Change Details
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging into the relevant area and choosing the appropiate options from the menu. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
Cookies
Like many web sites, this web site sets and uses
cookies to enhance your user experience -- to remember your personal
settings, for instance. Advertisements may display on this web site
and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer; such cookies
are subject to the privacy policy of the parties providing the
advertisement. However, the parties providing the advertising do not
have access to this site's cookies. These parties usually use
non-personally-identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information
about your visits to this site.
Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to
your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the
Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
[ Back ]
